export const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    options: [
      "Virtual DOM",
      "Original DOM",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Virtual DOM",
  },
  {
    question: "Who created React.js?",
    options: ["Jordan Mike", "Jordan Walke", "Tim Lee ", "Jordan Lee"],
    correctAnswer: "Jordan Walke",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following acts as the input of a class-based component?",
    options: ["Class", "Props", "Factory", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "Props",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is correct about prop in react?",
    options: [
      "Can be changed inside another component",
      "Can be changed inside the component",
      "Cannot be changed in the component",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cannot be changed in the component",
  },
  {
    question: "What does props stand for?",
    options: [
      "Proper Arguments",
      "Properties",
      "Proper Return Values",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Properties",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Babel?",
    options: ["Compiler", "Interpreter", "Both A and B", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswer: "Compiler",
  },
  {
    question: "JSX Stands for?",
    options: [
      "Javscript Extension",
      "Javascript",
      "Javascript XML",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Javascript XML",
  },
  {
    question: "Which method is used to render a React component to the DOM? ",
    options: [
      "renderComponent() ",
      "ReactDOM.render() ",
      "React.render() ",
      "component.render() ",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "ReactDOM.render()",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which hook is used to add state to functional components in React? ",
    options: ["useEffect ", "useContext ", "useReducer", "useState"],
    correctAnswer: "useState",
  },
  {
    question: "How many types of components are there in react? ",
    options: ["1 ", "2 ", "3", "4"],
    correctAnswer: "2",
  },
];
